International Fur and Leather Workers Union Records 5676
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- W General, 1936-1954 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  broadsides re Wagner-Steagall Housing Bill; form letter from Washington State Fur Dealers' Association re outside organizations coming to form a union; minutes of Resort Management Committee (White Lake), March, May 1954; financial correspondence re White Lake Lodge; and routine correspondence.
- W General, 1936-1954 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- W General, 1936-1954 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- W General, 1936-1954 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Y General, 1935-1947 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Z General, 1937-1954 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  financial statements of the International Fur and Leather Workers Union.
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Financial Reports, 1913-1946 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Financial Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  financial reports of the Fur Division, IFLWU.
- Weekly financial reports of the Joint Council, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Financial reports of the Leather Division, IFLWU, 1947-1953 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Death Benefits, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  death claims paid and rejections
- Miscellaneous bills, receipts, statements, etc. A, 1937-1943 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. Addressograph, 1937-1942 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. Addressograph, 1937-1942 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. Addressograph, 1937-1942 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - B, misc., 1937-1943 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - Bartel, Philip., 1936-1940 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. Bonding, 1939-1940 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  correspondence and lists re Bonding individuals in the union.
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - C, misc., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - C, misc., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - D, misc., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - E, misc., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - F-K., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - Income Tax., 1931-1943 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - L, misc., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - M, misc., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - N, misc., 1943 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - New York Telephone Co., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - Norwood Co., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - P, misc., 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - Post Office., 1937-1943 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - Post Office., 1937-1943 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - Post Office., 1937-1943 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - Publication Press., 1940-1943 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - R, misc., 1937-1940 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - S, misc., 1935-1939 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - United Air Lines., 1939-1940 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc. - V-Z., 1936-1940 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Financial - Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc., 1938-1951 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Financial - Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc., 1938-1951 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Financial - Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc., 1938-1951 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Financial - Misc. bills, receipts, statements, etc., 1938-1951 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Account Books, 1913-1948 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  volumes for International Union; local; income from locals, salaries, expenses, death benefits, etc.; per capita by month.
- Account Books, 1922-1939 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  volumes for Local 66; Local 67; Locals 20-51; Local 60-63; Local 25; Local 58; Expenditures for New Brunswick Strike and Rabbit Industry; Expenditures re Montreal Strike.
- Local 2 (Brooklyn, New York), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  "Proceedings - Appeal of Local 2," 12/4/51, 60 p., 2 copies.
- Local 2 (Brooklyn, New York), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Local 2 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  correspondence re slowdown at the Alaska Chemical Corp., 1947; agreement; routine correspondence.
- Local 2 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Local 2 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Local 2 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Local 2 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Local 2 (Brooklyn, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  financial statements.
- Local 3 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  includes list of members in good standing, enrollment cards, form letters and routine correspondence.
- Local 3 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Local 3 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Local 3 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Local 3 (Brooklyn, New York), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Local 3 (Brooklyn, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Local 4 (Brooklyn, New York), 1937-1945 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  sample agreement, 1937; and routine correspondence.
- Local 4 (Brooklyn, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Local 5 (Morgan City, Louisiana), 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  routine correspondence, including a telegram asking B. Gold to investigate organizers Chan and Metz.
- Local 10, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  National Labor Relations Board order dismissing petition re Palmer Packing Co. vs UFLWU, Local 10.
- Local 21 (Peabody, Massachusetts), 1939-1954 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  Massachusetts Organizational Committee's report by Mr. Chamouris, Chairman, 3 p.; proceedings in matter of appeal of E. Driscoll to Executive Board, Leather Division, UFLWU, 10/2/54, 73 p.
- Local 22 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1937-1942 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  membership lists; routine correspondence.
- Local 22 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1937-1942 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Local 22 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1937-1942 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Local 22 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Local 25 (Newark, New Jersey), 1924-1943 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  correspondence re local elections (1924) and testimony re election of officers, 7 p., 1924; extensive correspondence, including data sheet, article re Vice-President Milton Corbet (also a local officer) - misuse of local funds; reports, news releases and correspondence re International's suspension of local officers and taking over the local 1926-28; letter from M. Langer, Business agent to Sub- Committee, General Executive Board, IFLWU, re retaining M. Corbet as International Vice-President after removing him as a local officer due to misuse of office 12/1/26; correspondence re amalgamation of Local 25 and Local 58, 1928; and routine correspondence.
- Local 25 (Newark, New Jersey), 1924-1943 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Local 25 (Newark, New Jersey), 1924-1943 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Local 25 (Newark, New Jersey), 1924-1943 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Local 25 (Newark, New Jersey), 1939-1941 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Local 27 (Newark, New Jersey), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  correspondence re libel suit by AFL.
- Local 30 (Boston, Massachusetts), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  correspondence re a strike, 1926; internal strife due to some local officers' loyalty to the expelled Joint Board vs. the International; letter and petition asking the International to take over the local, 1/24/29; reorganization of the local; and routine correspondence.
- Local 30 (Boston, Massachusetts), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Local 30 (Boston, Massachusetts), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Local 30 (Boston, Massachusetts), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Local 30 (Boston, Massachusetts), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Local 30 (Boston, Massachusetts), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Local 30 (Boston, Massachusetts), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Local 30 (Boston, Massachusetts), 1915-1947 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Local 30 (Boston, Massachusetts), 1938-1941 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Local 31 (Overland, Missouri), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Local 31 (Overland, Missouri), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Local 31 (Overland, Missouri), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Local 31 (Overland, Missouri), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Local 34 (Hoboken, New Jersey), 1939 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  report of Leather Workers' Division Executive Board members on investigation of the administration of organizer Joseph F. Massidda re financial transactions, 11 p., no date.
- Local 35 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1915-1942 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  correspondence re dissolution of Local 40 and its members joining Local 35, 1915; and routine correspondence.
- Local 35 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Local 37 (Elkland, Pennsylvania), 1939-1941 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  routine correspondence; pamphlet "We Accuse," 1943, 16 p. re Elkland Leather Co.; broadsides; "History of the Labor Struggle in the Elkland Leather Co.," 3 p., by Henry Van Zile.
- Local 37 (Elkland, Pennsylvania), 1939 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Local 38 (Detroit, Michigan), 1938-1954 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  includes an Audit Report for 7/1/46-6/30/47; correspondence between B. Gold and Harold Shapiro, organizer, re Gold's trial and beliefs, 1/54; and routine correspondence.
- Local 38 (Detroit, Michigan), 1938-1954 (Box 20, Folder 49)
- Local 38 (Detroit, Michigan), 1938-1954 (Box 20, Folder 50)
- Local 38 (Detroit, Michigan), 1938-1954 (Box 20, Folder 51)
- Local 38 (Detroit, Michigan), 1938-1954 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Local 38 (Detroit, Michigan), 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 53)
- Local 39 (Buffalo, New York), 1939-1946 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  misc. financial statements.
- Local 40 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1937-1942 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  membership list, weekly financial sheets, routine correspondence.
- Local 40 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1940-1942 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Local 41 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 3a)
- Local 43 (Chicago, Illinois), 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  financial statements, leaflets, broadsides, membership list, routine correspondence.
- Local 43 (Chicago, Illinois), 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Local 43 (Chicago, Illinois), 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Local 44 (Gowanda, New York), 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  routine correspondence; one issue, May 1940, of the local's publication, The Tanner; financial statements.
- Local 44 (Gowanda, New York), 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Local 44 (Gowanda, New York), 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1925 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  includes report to General Executive Board, January 5, 1925, handwritten; letters to Kaufman from J. Millstein, Manager Local 45 re lack of work, agreements to expire, meetings, organizing, unemployment insurance plan, Montreal situation, problems between International and Joint Board; local's officials dispute broadside; one issue The Chicago Fur Worker, October 25.
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1926 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  petition against local officers re corruption; correspondence re problems within the local and strike; Local 45 members being expelled because of opposition to Millstein Administration; Millstein calls Gold "double-crosser" in telegram, August 3; August 25 letter to Schactman from Millstein re meeting of the "left wingers"; Irving I. Israelson becomes Manager of Local - question re conduct of election of officers; and routine.
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1927-1937 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  continued correspondence between Schactman, Israelson and Millstein re local activities; special convention issue of The Chicago Fur Worker, May 1937.
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1938 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  correspondence re routine local activities.
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1940 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1941 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1942 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1945 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  resolution condemning leadership of New York Fur Manufacturers Association; correspondence re agreements reached; and misc.
- Local 45 (Chicago, Illinois), 1938-1942 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Locals 46 and 47 (Canada), 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  handwritten report of Local 46, undated; handwritten report of Local 47, undated; and routine.
- Local 48 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1938 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Local 48 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Local 48 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1940 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Local 48 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1941 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Local 48 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1942 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  correspondence re local's 11th Anniversary celebration; telegram to Gold from local pledging continued support to leadership.
- Local 48 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1938-1941 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Local 49 (Seattle, Washington), 1938 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  routine correspondence; form letter sent to all local members re asking for support, etc.; membership list.
- Local 49 (Seattle, Washington), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Local 49 (Seattle, Washington), 1940 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Local 49 (Seattle, Washington), 1941 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  routine correspondence, includes a dues booklet.
- Local 49 (Seattle, Washington), 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Local 51 (Baltimore, Maryland), 1939-1941 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  routine correspondence and financial statements.
- Local 51 (Baltimore, Maryland), 1939-1941 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Local 52 (St. Paul, Minnesota), 1938-1945 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Local 52 (St. Paul, Minnesota), 1938-1945 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Local 53 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1926-1928 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  correspondence re problems within local leadership, strike, local officials slander the International; 3 p. information sheet "New Communist Betrayal of Philadelphia Fur Workers"; Local 53 suspension from International.
- Local 53 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1937 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  membership list.
- Local 53 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1938 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Local 53 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Local 53 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1940 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Local 53 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1941 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Local 53 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1942-1945 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Local 53 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1938-1941 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- Local 54 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1926-1939 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  1926 letter, letterhead: Newark, New Jersey, #54; and routine.
- Local 54 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1940-1942 (Box 21, Folder 45)
- Local 54 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1938-1941 (Box 21, Folder 46)
- Local 55 (Buffalo, New York), 1938 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  membership list and routine correspondence.
- Local 55 (Buffalo, New York), 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 48)
- Local 55 (Buffalo, New York), 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 49)
- Local 55 (Buffalo, New York), 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- Local 56 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1939-1941 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  financial statements and routine correspondence.
- Local 57 (St. Paul, Minnesota), 1938-1942 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Local 57 (St. Paul, Minnesota), 1938-1942 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Local 58 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1928-1942 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  originally Brooklyn, New York; correspondence re Brooklyn Local 58 suspension from the International Union, 1928; correspondence to International from Fur Dressers and Dyers Union in Toronto applying for affiliation; and routine.
- Local 58 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1928-1942 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Local 58 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1928-1942 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Local 58 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1936-1942 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Local 59 (Brooklyn, New York), 1925-1938 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Local 59 (Brooklyn, New York), 1925-1938 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Local 59 (Brooklyn, New York), 1925-1938 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Local 59 (Brooklyn, New York), 1936-1938 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Local 61 (New York, New York), 1938-1941 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  routine correspondence and membership list.
- Local 61 (New York, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Local 62 (Danbury, Connecticut), 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  membership list, broadside and routine correspondence.
- Local 64 (New York, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  membership lists, routine correspondence.
- Local 64 (New York, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Local 64 (New York, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Local 64 (New York, New York), 1939-1941 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Local 65 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1936-1941 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Local 65 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1936-1941 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Local 66 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1937-1940 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  membership list, report of complaints and shop meetings, routine correspondence - includes Local 66-67.
- Local 66 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1937-1940 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Local 66 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1938-1942 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Local 66-67 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1935-1954 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  correspondence re bargaining with employers in Montreal for new contract; membership list; reports on activities; and routine.
- Local 66-67 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1935-1954 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Local 66-67 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1935-1954 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Local 66-67 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1935-1954 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Local 66-67 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1937 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Local 67 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1941 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  membership list; and routine correspondence.
- Local 67 (Montreal, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1940 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Local 68 (Quebec, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1945 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  reports on routine local activity; and other routine correspondence.
- Local 68 (Quebec, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1945 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Local 68 (Quebec, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1945 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Local 68 (Quebec, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1945 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Local 68 (Quebec, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1945 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Local 68 (Quebec, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1945 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Local 68 (Quebec, Quebec, Canada), 1936-1941 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Local 69 (Pittsburg, Pennsylvania), 1936-1947 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  reports of organizing activities, newsletter, clippings and correspondence re strike, 1936; membership; financial statements; and routine correspondence.
- Local 69 (Pittsburg, Pennsylvania), 1936-1947 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Local 69 (Pittsburg, Pennsylvania), 1936-1947 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Local 69 (Pittsburg, Pennsylvania), 1936-1947 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Local 69 (Pittsburg, Pennsylvania), 1936-1947 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Local 69 (Pittsburg, Pennsylvania), 1936-1947 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Local 69 (Pittsburg, Pennsylvania), 1936-1942 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  financial statements, article.
- Local 69 (Pittsburg, Pennsylvania), 1936-1942 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Local 69 (Pittsburg, Pennsylvania), 1936-1942 (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Greek Fur Workers Local - broadsides; Sub-Committee minutes re the "Greek situation" includes a brief history of Local 70, 3/20/27; form letters; financial statements; extensive correspondence re the strained relationship between Local 70 and the Joint Council, including news release and resolution, 1936; correspondence re Greek Fur Workers' Local 70 members working in Joint Council shops; newsletters; minutes of the Joint Conference Committee, 3/24/37, (Local 70 and United Fur Manufacturers Association); court document; membership list; court decision, United vs. Gold, 7/14/39, 2 p.; correspondence and newsletters by the newly organized American Federation of Fur Workers, Local 22,385, who accuse Local 70 and its leaders of being under Communist influence; court document, James Stephenson, et. al. vs. United Fur Manufacturers, 5/23/41, 6 p.; pamphlet "The Greek Americans in the Fur Industry" in Greek, 1963, 16 p.; and routine correspondence.
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1937 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  Greek Fur Workers Local - financial statements.
- Local 70 (New York, New York), 1936-1941 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  Greek Fur Workers Local - publications - scattered issues of Local 70 monthly publications (in Greek).
- Local 70 (New York, New York) - Greek Fur Workers Local - misc. (Box 23, Folder 20)
  (Greek and English) resolutions, broadsides, articles, handwritten notes; report by the National Credit Office "The Woolen and Worsted Industry," 1926, 11 p.; agreement, United Fur Manufacturers Association and Fur Workers Brotherhood of New York, 1926; petitions; structure chart of the Furriers Joint Council of New York.
- Local 70 (New York, New York) - Greek Fur Workers Local - misc. (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Local 70 (New York, New York) - Greek Fur Workers Local - misc. (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Local 70 (New York, New York) - Greek Fur Workers Local - misc. (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Local 70 (New York, New York) - Greek Fur Workers Local (Box 23, Folder 24)
  photos removed - placed in Box 32, ff 10.
- Local 71 (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  reports on organizing and negotiations; financial report; and routine correspondence.
- Local 71 (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Local 71 (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Local 71 (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Local 71 (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Local 71 (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Local 71 (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Local 71 (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1936-1941 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Local 72 (Washington, D.C.), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  correspondence re reorganization of Washington furriers, 1936; resolution; and routine.
- Local 72 (Washington, D.C.), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Local 72 (Washington, D.C.), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 35)